

CONTACT

: +44 7580199079

: angelknela5@hotmail.co.uk

: https://www.linkedin.com/in/angel-canela

: https://github.com/angelknla

: 1025A Garratt Lane, London, United Kingdom, SW17 0LN

PERSONAL SKILLS

-	••••	nunication	
-		y to Work.	
-	Decis	ion Making	
-	Time	Management	
-	Confl	ict Resolution	_
-	Leade		
	Adap	tability	

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Coding Languages:

- JAVA, TypeScript, JavaScript,
- HTML5/CSS3, XML, Python.

Frameworks/Systems:

- React JS, Redux, Node JS,
- Express JS, Next.JS, Bootstrap, jQuery, Jest.
- $\hbox{- Git Version Control, Styled Components, GraphQl.}\\$

Database Technologies:

- MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Mongoose.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

English			
95%			
Spanish			
100%			
Japanese			
85%			
Korean			
200/			

ANGEL CANELA

Junior Software Engineer

PROFILE -

I am an innovative problem solver that likes to test and experiment with thorough analysis and evaluation, confirming ideas and creating step-by-step plans. I make sure I expand my thinking forward by partnering up with other team members who are different from me.

My contribution to the team is to create options in the form of practical solutions, evaluating and then uncovering all the factors that go into a successful plan for implementation.

Familiar working with Agile ways of working such as Scrum and Kanban, experience working with computer systems, data structures, analysing system requirements, applications architecture and developing Android as well as Web-based applications

EDUCATION –

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND MATHEMATICS.

The Open University 2017 – 2021. Grade: 2:1

- Key modules: Computer systems, Software engineering, Problem Solving with Algorithms, Pure Mathematics, Java Programming, Data Structures.

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN MECHANICAL ENGINEERING.

University of Oviedo 2007 – 2012, Grade 2:1

- Industrial and Mechanical Engineering studies.

EXPERIENCE -

JUNIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER (FE)

Kurt Geiger / London - July 2021- Till Date

Responsible for supporting the software development team in all aspects of the development, testing and implementation of the product:

- Writing and debugging code.
- Troubleshooting software issues.
- Developing innovative solutions.
- Attending developer meetings.
- Participating in code reviews and quality assurance activities.
- Participating in estimation discussions with the product team.
- Building reusable React components for the web platform.
- Creation and maintenance of the project Storybook, documenting reusable components

SOFTWARE ENGINEER INTERN

Kurt Geiger / London - Sept 2020 - July 2021

Software Engineer Intern, assisting the development team with software design and learning the codebase. Tasks include:

- Bug fixes
- Maintenance of the site
- $\operatorname{Building}$ experiences using the eCommerce platform $\operatorname{Qubit}.$
- Participating in code reviews and quality assurance activities

CABIN CREW

Cathay Pacific Airways / London - May 2013 - Sept 2020

My main role was to:

- To ensure security and safety responsibilities are performed to the highest standards
- Be an ambassador of the Cathay Pacific brand.
- Create effective working relationships with colleagues to foster teamwork.
- Top 10% performance

JAPANESE TEACHER

Educatiò / Spain 2010 - 2013

Undertaking full time job while still in university. Teaching Japanese to students from different backgrounds and develop business relationships with clients (students).